Guide to the Josef Silverstein papers, [ca. 1950-1990]
Silverstein, Josef papers, [ca. 1950-1990]
- Series I. Correspondence and Research Files
  - SEA Conference, International Security in SEA: Current Problems and Prospects for Preparation (1 of 8), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - SEA Conference, International Security in SEA: Current Problems and Prospects for Preparation (2 of 8), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - SEA Conference, International Security in SEA: Current Problems and Prospects for Preparation (3 of 8), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - SEA Conference, International Security in SEA: Current Problems and Prospects for Preparation (4 of 8), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - SEA Conference, International Security in SEA: Current Problems and Prospects for Preparation (5 of 8), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - SEA Conference, International Security in SEA: Current Problems and Prospects for Preparation (6 of 8), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - SEA Conference, International Security in SEA: Current Problems and Prospects for Preparation (7 of 8), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - SEA Conference, International Security in SEA: Current Problems and Prospects for Preparation (8 of 8), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Einstein Conference, Boston (1 of 3), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Einstein Conference, Boston (2 of 3), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Einstein Conference, Boston (3 of 3), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Kuala Lampur Conference (1 of 6), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Kuala Lampur Conference (2 of 6), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Kuala Lampur Conference (3 of 6), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Kuala Lampur Conference (4 of 6), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Kuala Lampur Conference (5 of 6), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Kuala Lampur Conference (6 of 6), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Asia Watch, New York, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Defense Intelligence Conference (1 of 3), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Defense Intelligence Conference (2 of 3), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Defense Intelligence Conference (3 of 3), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Germany Conference/Hofgeisman (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Germany Conference/Hofgeisman (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Kota Kinabalu Meeting (1 of 7), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Kota Kinabalu Meeting (2 of 7), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Kota Kinabalu Meeting (3 of 7), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Kota Kinabalu Meeting (4 of 7), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Kota Kinabalu Meeting (5 of 7), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Kota Kinabalu Meeting (6 of 7), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Kota Kinabalu Meeting (7 of 7), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Oxford Project (1 of 7), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Oxford Project (2 of 7), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Oxford Project (3 of 7), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Oxford Project (4 of 7), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Oxford Project (5 of 7), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Oxford Project (6 of 7), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Oxford Project (7 of 7), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Asian Survey, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Association of Asian Studies Meeting (Washington), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Bangkok Constitution Conference, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - The Carter Center (1 of 10), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - The Carter Center (2 of 10), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - The Carter Center (3 of 10), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - The Carter Center (4 of 10), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - The Carter Center (5 of 10), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - The Carter Center (6 of 10), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - The Carter Center (7 of 10), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - The Carter Center (8 of 10), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - The Carter Center (9 of 10), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - The Carter Center (10 of 10), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Defense Intelligence Conference (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Defense Intelligence Conference (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Holland (1 of 3), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Holland (2 of 3), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Holland (3 of 3), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Cornell, Aung San (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Cornell, Aung San (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Cornell, Aung San (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Cornell, Aung San (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Institute of Southeast Asian Studies, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Southeast Asia, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Washington Meeting, State Department, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Ve-Tavoy Railway-Mon State, 1994, April (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - “Current History” (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - “Current History” (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Manila Constitution Meeting, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Penn State Meeting, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Rangoon Conference (1 of 3), 1995 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Rangoon Conference (2 of 3), 1995 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Rangoon Conference (3 of 3), 1995 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Simon Frazer Lecture, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Toronto Conference, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Swiss Conference (1 of 3), 1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Swiss Conference (2 of 3), 1995 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Swiss Conference (3 of 3), 1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Washington D.C., Chamber of Commerce, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - University of Calgary Conference, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Reprints of Burma Newspaper (1 of 3), 1996, May 1-29 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Reprints of Burma Newspaper (2 of 3), 1996, May 1-29 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Reprints of Burma Newspaper (3 of 3), 1996, May 1-29 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Ebert Foundation, New York City Meeting, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Harvard Project (1 of 3), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Harvard Project (2 of 3), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Harvard Project (3 of 3), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - New Delhi Conference, Restoration of Democracy in Burma (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - New Delhi Conference, Restoration of Democracy in Burma (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - The Woods Conference (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - The Woods Conference (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Wurfec Toronto Conference (1 of 8), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Wurfec Toronto Conference (2 of 8), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Wurfec Toronto Conference (3 of 8), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Wurfec Toronto Conference (4 of 8), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Wurfec Toronto Conference (5 of 8), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Wurfec Toronto Conference (6 of 8), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Wurfec Toronto Conference (7 of 8), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Wurfec Toronto Conference (8 of 8), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Bangkok, Constructive Engagement (1 of 4), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Bangkok, Constructive Engagement (2 of 4), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Bangkok, Constructive Engagement (3 of 4), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Bangkok, Constructive Engagement (4 of 4), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Burma Economy Seminar, Washington (1 of 3), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Burma Economy Seminar, Washington (2 of 3), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Burma Economy Seminar, Washington (3 of 3), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Freedom House (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Freedom House (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Kutztown Meeting, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - World Affairs Conference, University of Colorado (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - World Affairs Conference, University of Colorado (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Bonn Conference (1 of 8), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Bonn Conference (2 of 8), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Bonn Conference (3 of 8), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Bonn Conference (4 of 8), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Bonn Conference (5 of 8), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Bonn Conference (6 of 8), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Bonn Conference (7 of 8), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Bonn Conference (8 of 8), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - International Labor Organization Material (1 of 5), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - International Labor Organization Material (2 of 5), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - International Labor Organization Material (3 of 5), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - International Labor Organization Material (4 of 5), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - International Labor Organization Material (5 of 5), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Burma Training Conference Bangkok, Thailand, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Fort Wayne Burma Meeting, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - World Affairs Conference, University of Colorado (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - World Affairs Conference, University of Colorado (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - World Bank Report, Myanmar: An Economic and Social Assessment (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - World Bank Report, Myanmar: An Economic and Social Assessment (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Amnesty International, Justice on Trial (1 of 3), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Amnesty International, Justice on Trial (2 of 3), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Amnesty International, Justice on Trial (3 of 3), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Drugs and Business (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Drugs and Business (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Kyi May Kaung Manuscript (1 of 7), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Kyi May Kaung Manuscript (2 of 7), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Kyi May Kaung Manuscript (3 of 7), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Kyi May Kaung Manuscript (4 of 7), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Kyi May Kaung Manuscript (5 of 7), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Kyi May Kaung Manuscript (6 of 7), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Kyi May Kaung Manuscript (7 of 7), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Maung Pho Shoke-Why did Khin Sa’s MTA Exchange Arms for Peace? (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Maung Pho Shoke-Why did Khin Sa’s MTA Exchange Arms for Peace? (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Burma Economic Watch, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Cho Cho Win Asylum Case, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Houtman, “Buddhist Political Rhetoric in Burma”, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Kyin Zar Wai Asylum Case, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Political Change in Southeast Asia, ISEAS (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Political Change in Southeast Asia, ISEAS (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Reconciliation Without Capitulation, NBR Report and Critique (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Reconciliation Without Capitulation, NBR Report and Critique (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Zarni-May Oo Report, “Common Problems Shared Responsibilities: Citizen’s Quest for National Reconciliation in Burma/Myanmar (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Zarni-May Oo Report, “Common Problems Shared Responsibilities: Citizen’s Quest for National Reconciliation in Burma/Myanmar (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Aung Khent Asylum Case (1 of 6), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Aung Khent Asylum Case (2 of 6), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Aung Khent Asylum Case (3 of 6), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Aung Khent Asylum Case (4 of 6), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Aung Khent Asylum Case (5 of 6), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Aung Khent Asylum Case (6 of 6), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Denis Kaito Asylum Case, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Human Rights, Mons, Catwalk to the Barracks, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Informal U.N. Meeting, Century Club (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Informal U.N. Meeting, Century Club (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Pho Thawda Asylum Case (1 of 3), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Pho Thawda Asylum Case (2 of 3), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Pho Thawda Asylum Case (1 of 3), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Nang Mo Hom Asylum Case (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Nang Mo Hom Asylum Case (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - U.N. Havec-Tutu Report (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - U.N. Havec-Tutu Report (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - U.S. Department of State Human Rights Report, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Current Economic Conditions in Burma, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Daniel Vau Cei Han Asylum Case, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Khua Hlue, T. Asylum Case, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - September News and Correspondence (1 of 5), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - September News and Correspondence (2 of 5), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - September News and Correspondence (3 of 5), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - September News and Correspondence (4 of 5), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - September News and Correspondence (5 of 5), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - October News and Correspondence (1 of 4), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - October News and Correspondence (2 of 4), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - October News and Correspondence (3 of 4), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - October News and Correspondence (4 of 4), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - November News and Correspondence (1 of 2), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - November News and Correspondence (2 of 2), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - December News and Correspondence, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Saffron Revolution Aftermath (1 of 4), 2007 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Saffron Revolution Aftermath (2 of 4), 2007 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Saffron Revolution Aftermath (3 of 4), 2007 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Saffron Revolution Aftermath (4 of 4), 2007 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Talk on “The Tragedies of Burma”, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Pinheiro Reports and Commentary (1 of 4), 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Pinheiro Reports and Commentary (2 of 4), 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Pinheiro Reports and Commentary (3 of 4), 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Pinheiro Reports and Commentary (4 of 4), 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Andrew Selth, Burma’s Saffron Revolution, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Brief on Preliminary Assessment of Damage on Agricultural Production Caused by Cyclone Nargis and Recovery Plan, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Burma Constitution (1 of 3), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Burma Constitution (2 of 3), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Burma Constitution (3 of 3), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Constitution (1 of 5), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Constitution (2 of 5), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Constitution (3 of 5), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Constitution (4 of 5), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Constitution (5 of 5), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Mary Meng Thla Asylum Case (1 of 4), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Mary Meng Thla Asylum Case (2 of 4), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Mary Meng Thla Asylum Case (3 of 4), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Mary Meng Thla Asylum Case (4 of 4), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Political Prisoners Report, “The Future in the Dark” by Bo Kyi, AAPP, Aung Din, U.S. Campaign for Burma (1 of 2), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Political Prisoners Report, “The Future in the Dark” by Bo Kyi, AAPP, Aung Din, U.S. Campaign for Burma (2 of 2), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Thailand, Chiang Mai (1 of 2), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Thailand, Chiang Mai (2 of 2), 2008 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Original and Legal Documents, Late British (1 of 2), 1940s-1950 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Original and Legal Documents, Late British (2 of 2), 1940s-1950 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Electrical Advisory Committee—British India (1 of 7), 1943-1948 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Electrical Advisory Committee—British India (2 of 7), 1943-1948 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Electrical Advisory Committee—British India (3 of 7), 1943-1948 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Electrical Advisory Committee—British India (4 of 7), 1943-1948 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Electrical Advisory Committee—British India (5 of 7), 1943-1948 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Electrical Advisory Committee—British India (6 of 7), 1943-1948 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Electrical Advisory Committee—British India (7 of 7), 1943-1948 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Air Transportation Act, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Man The Wolf of Man, Novel By U Nu, 1950s (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - “Introducing Burma”, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - History of Burma Economy, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Notes, Interviews, Original Documents, Constitutions (1 of 3), 1955 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Notes, Interviews, Original Documents, Constitutions (2 of 3), 1955 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Notes, Interviews, Original Documents, Constitutions (3 of 3), 1955 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Reports on Burma, Tobacco and Soil Deterioration, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Original Seminar Papers on Burma, Foreign Policy, and Various other Papers (1 of 3), 1995-1956 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Original Seminar Papers on Burma, Foreign Policy, and Various other Papers (2 of 3), 1995-1956 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Original Seminar Papers on Burma, Foreign Policy, and Various other Papers (3 of 3), 1995-1956 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - British Treaty Materials and Sino-Burma Issues, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Max McGrath Article (Burmese), 1956 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Notes on Caretaker Government (Ne Win), 1956 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Union of Burma Airways, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence with Burmese Embassy, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Asian History for Seminar, by B.R. Pearn, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Government Exchange of Statements (U Nu), Original Newspaper with Ne Win Declaration and Rules, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Burma Translation Society, Original Documents, Late 1950s-1960s (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Sino-Burmese Materials, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Sino-Burma Conflict from Burmese Point of View (1 of 4), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Sino-Burma Conflict from Burmese Point of View (2 of 4), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Sino-Burma Conflict from Burmese Point of View (3 of 4), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Sino-Burma Conflict from Burmese Point of View (4 of 4), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Southeast Asian History Course at University of Malaya, Malaysia Essays, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence (1 of 7), 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence (2 of 7), 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence (3 of 7), 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence (4 of 7), 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence (5 of 7), 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence (6 of 7), 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence (7 of 7), 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Singapore Institute Correspondence (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Singapore Institute Correspondence (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Lansin Period, Ne Win Party (1 of 2), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Lansin Period, Ne Win Party (2 of 2), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Youth, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Economy—Ne Win Period, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Peasants—Ne Win Period, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Long and Short Term Economic Policies, Burma Socialist Program Party (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Long and Short Term Economic Policies, Burma Socialist Program Party (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Htun Myaing and Others, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1980 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1980 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1980 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1980 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - State Department, ASEAN Tour (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - State Department, ASEAN Tour (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - ISEAS Conference Papers Workshop on Towards A Durable Regional Stability (1 of 7), 1985 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - ISEAS Conference Papers Workshop on Towards A Durable Regional Stability (2 of 7), 1985 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - ISEAS Conference Papers Workshop on Towards A Durable Regional Stability (3 of 7), 1985 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - ISEAS Conference Papers Workshop on Towards A Durable Regional Stability (4 of 7), 1985 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - ISEAS Conference Papers Workshop on Towards A Durable Regional Stability (5 of 7), 1985 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - ISEAS Conference Papers Workshop on Towards A Durable Regional Stability (6 of 7), 1985 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - ISEAS Conference Papers Workshop on Towards A Durable Regional Stability (7 of 7), 1985 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Washington Narcotics Conference, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Smith, Martin; Burma: And the Politics of Ethnicity (1 of 10) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Martin; Burma: And the Politics of Ethnicity (2 of 10) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Martin; Burma: And the Politics of Ethnicity (3 of 10) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Martin; Burma: And the Politics of Ethnicity (4 of 10) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Martin; Burma: And the Politics of Ethnicity (5 of 10) (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Martin; Burma: And the Politics of Ethnicity (6 of 10) (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Martin; Burma: And the Politics of Ethnicity (7 of 10) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Martin; Burma: And the Politics of Ethnicity (8 of 10) (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Martin; Burma: And the Politics of Ethnicity (9 of 10) (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Martin; Burma: And the Politics of Ethnicity (10 of 10) (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Tonkin; Derek; 2008 Myanmar Constitution: Analysis and Assessment (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Morse, Stephen A.; The Development of Kachin Nationalism and the Union of Burma (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Kin Oung; “Blood of the Martyrs” A story About Carnage in Burma (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - La Nangzing; My Life in Jails Under Burmese Rule (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Burmese Language (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Lintner, Bertil; The Rise and Fall of the Communist Party of Burma (CPB) (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Yang Li (Jackie Yang); The House of Yang, Guardians of an Unknown Frontier (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Chao-Tzang Yanghwe; Ne Win’s Tatmadaw Dictatorship (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Silverstein Notebooks (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Silverstein Notebooks (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Constitution of the Republic of the Union of Myanmar, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Josef Silverstein’s Burmese Dictionary Supplement (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Morse, Stephen A.; The Development of Kachin Nationalism and the Union of Burma, April 14, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Aye Kyaw; The Voice of Young Burma (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Lintner, Bertil’s “Journey to the Land of Jade. Burma Behind the Lines of Kachin and Communist Rebels” (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - La Nangzing’s “A brief autobiography” (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Lintner, Bertil’s “State of Revolt. How Burma Became the World’s Biggest Heroin Producer” (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Series II. Newspaper Clippings
  - Burma Pre=Independent British India Clippings (1 of 4), 1904-1950 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Burma Pre=Independent British India Clippings (2 of 4), 1904-1950 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Burma Pre=Independent British India Clippings (3 of 4), 1904-1950 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Burma Pre=Independent British India Clippings (4 of 4), 1904-1950 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Burma Parliamentary Election Act, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Politics in Independent Burma, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Operation Inside China, 1950-1951 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - National Achieve-Washington D.C., 1950-1954 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Thailand KMT, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - French: I.C., Nehru’s Intervention, 1950/1951 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Burma Diplomatics, 1950, 1953, and 1961 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Internal Politics, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Appeal to the U.N., 1953 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Eisenhower’s March, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Chiang’s Line and Arm in: Drussout, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Post Karan Armistice, 1953-1954 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Lecture on Burma, 1953/1954 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Post Korean War, 1953-1960 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Burma Miscellaneous, 1953-1975 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Burma, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Burma News Clippings, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - KMT and Insurgency Trade Off, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Material, Original Documents, and Josef Silverstein Notes on David Marshall as Chief Ministry of Singapore (1 of 3), 1954-1956 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Material, Original Documents, and Josef Silverstein Notes on David Marshall as Chief Ministry of Singapore (2 of 3), 1954-1956 (Box 25, Folder 23)